

(804) 929-7374 taylorradtke@gmail.com | www.taylorradtke.com | Alexandria, VA

SKILLS

W3C Validated HTML5

CSS3, SCSS, SASSS

Bourbon / Neat Foundation Skeleton Bootstrap

JavaScript, ES6

Angular 2+ jQuery Babel React Gatsby Node.js

Vue

PHP, Wordpress

Theme Development Advanced Custom Fields Admin/Plugin Setup SQL Management **Custom Functionality** Inheritance Model

Web Design

UI/UX Design Sketching Interaction Design Grid & Layout Wireframing Color Theory Rapid Prototyping Typography Usability Graphic Design

EDUCATION

2015 - PRESENT

General Assembly

Front-End Development Alexandria, VA

2011 - 2014

Virginia Commonwealth University

Information Systems Alexandria, VA

2009 - 2011

J. Sargeant Reynolds

Business (A.A.S) Richmond, VA

ABOUT ME

Taylor Radtke is a creative mind who specializes in minimal design that displays a bold message. After three plus years of marketing in the service industry, Taylor takes his social skills mastered from constructing cocktails through college to create a finished project that his client truly loves. Taylor has a great latitude of culture due to his upbringing in Southern California, before transitioning to the mid-Atlantic region to further his career and education. He is passionate about web-design as a functional piece of art, and strive to let his mind continue to peruse the beauty of the digital experience.

EXPERIENCE

JULY 2017 - PRESENT

Cisco Engineer

Herndon, VA

OCT 2016 – JULY 2017

AAPA

Full-Stack Web Developer Alexandria, VA

APR 2016 - OCT 2016

The Motley Fool Front-End Web Developer (Contractor) Alexandria, VA

Developed and designed microsites, newsletters. Developed and designed, and e-mail templates. Conducted BrowserStack usability testing for pages on all devices.

Created a completely dynamic Wordpress Theme used by hundreds

of different partners that brands all pages and components with

Completely redesigned website in under 4 months, on a new CMS.

Developed web site mock-ups for clients to ensure quality control

and client satisfaction before project development phase. Lead

Designer and Developer for Annual Conference Site.

their personal branding (Typography, brand colors, logo, etc)

NOV 2015 - APR 2016

Total Wine & More Digital Media Designer (Contractor) Bethesda, MD

Responsible for designing and maintaining web banners in various formats to be displayed on any device. Conducted analyses using Google Analytics and Google AdWords.

AWARDS / CERTIFICATIONS

Green Belt Security Certified

White Belt Security Certified

Spot Award, 50th Landing Page AAPA - 2017

Cisco - 2018

Cisco - 2018